Guide to the Paul Davidoff papers, 1951-1985
Davidoff, Paul papers, 1951-1985
- Series IX. Project files
  - Macklowe Project (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Published reports (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - CPC Reports on Discretionary Zoning Actions, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Lincoln West Project (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Literature on development cost (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Interview notes (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Policy analyses from other states (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Inclusionary Zoning- SEQRA & CEQRA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Inclusionary Zoning- other cities (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Vested rights (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Occupancy controls (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Mount Laurel II (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - AAFE Chinatown Suit (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Manhattan Bridge lawsuits (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Zoning Law- general (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - New York City Charter (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Section Liability, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Smith Haven Mall Affidavit - court version (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Shopping Center articles (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Bibliography/Lit. Search (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Shopping Center caselaw (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Prior Affidavit drafts (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Smith Haven Affidavit: final draft (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Mall drafts (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Smith Haven: site evaluation (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Smith Haven leases (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Mall Association minutes (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - National & New York City statistics (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Suffolk Census data (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Smith Haven Mall events (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Smith Haven Mall Case: court papers (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Shopping Mall literature (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Downtown Malls (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Yale Con. Law memos (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Suffolk maps (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Smith Haven Mall correspondence (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Expert Testimony schedule and billing (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Proposed settlement, Jan. 27, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Starrett Court papers (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Yonkers proposed settlement (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - New Hampshire Trial notes (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Zoning ordinances (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Atkinson final report- original (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Atkinson report drafts (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Research on HUD cost controls (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Starrett billing (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Response to Millgram questions (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Projects within a 6-mile radius (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Income data (Brooklyn & New York City), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Report drafts (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Notes on Millgram questions (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Notes on Newman response (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Rent Range vs. Income Range data (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Census profile: Starrett City, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Appendix (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Millgram Deposition Part II (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Davidoff Deposition Part II (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Zip Code maps (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Starrett draft I (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Starrett current file (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Deposition preparation (Paul) (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - State Division projects (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Starrett meetings (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Elise Deposition summary (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Starrett rent schedule (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Race & segregation literature (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Starrett correspondence & phone calls (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Starrett literature search (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Starrett testimony outline (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Starrett census data (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Newman report, etc. (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Starrett City (Box 22, Folder 36-37)
  - Davidoff (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Milgrim (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Reports (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Reports, etc. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Starrett Deposition materials (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Original: final Starrett report & appendices (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Starrett City (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Starrett Deposition (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Starrett City (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Calculations (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Starrett City Case (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Starrett City, Jan. 1984 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Starrett (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Davidoff Deposition continued, etc. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Yonkers Board of Education (expert testimony) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Yonkers Case (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Yonkers (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
  - Philip Tegeler (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Planners Press Manuscript - original (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Symposium authors (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Symposium (original) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Planners Press (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Legal Symposium (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Symposium expenses (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Registration list (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - NYC ABA mailing list (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - NYC NLIHC mailing list (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Advisory board (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Clearinghouse article drafts (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Pratt/CMA meetings (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Project descriptions & letters for distribution to public (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Project outlines (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence & phone calls (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Internal memoranda (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Neighborhood evaluation (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Project publicity & articles (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Zoning clippings (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Progress report to foundations, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Pratt/CMA testimony (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Conference preparation (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Morgan Guaranty Proposal (withdrawn) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Community Trust (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Fundraising correspondence (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Foundation correspondence (zoning), 1984 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - J.C. Penney Grant, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Penney Proposal, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Interim report (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Grant correspondence, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Implementation & conference proposals (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Symposium funding (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Development Comments Study Commission (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Complete-Sviridoff Commission testimony, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Proposal & budget (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Political implementation (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Series X. Articles, publications, etc.
  - HUD Coop. Agreement HA-6652 contract & official papers (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - HUD contract (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - MAI files - miscellany (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - MAI files - magazine articles (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - MAI files - articles & clippings (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - "Integrateduation" (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - "Advocacy planning-?", 1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - "Journal of American Institute of Planners", 1970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "Journal of American Institute of Planners", 1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - "Barns Miljo", 1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - "Clearing House Review", 1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - "Housing for Woodbridge" (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - SAI publications (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - MAI publications (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Books by others (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Series XI. Clippings from scrapbooks
  - Environment (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - National (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - RPA (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Transportations (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Connecticut, Long Island, New York City, Pennsylvania, Ridgefield, Connecticut (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut General (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Long Island (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - New York City (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Rockland (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey General (Box 26, Folder 14-17)
  - New Jersey General Randolph (Box 26, Folder 18-19)
  - New Jersey General Readington (Box 26, Folder 20-21)
  - New Jersey General Wayne (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey A-E A (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey A-E Bedminster (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey A-E Bergen County (Box 26, Folder 25-26)
  - New Jersey A-E Bernards Township (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey A-E East Brunswick (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - New Jersey Class Action- Franklin Lakes (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - New Jersey Class Action- Holmdel (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - New Jersey Class Action- Livingston (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - New Jersey Class Action- Madison (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - New Jersey Class Action- Mount Laurel (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - New Jersey Class Action (Box 26, Folder 34-35)
  - Westchester (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - UDC (Box 26, Folder 37-38)
  - Westchester General (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - White Plains (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Yonkers (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Yorktown (Box 26, Folder 42)